<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello! 
My name is Laura.
I’m a digital designer and&amp;nbsp;illustrator. on Laura Sinclair</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hello! 
My name is Laura.
I’m a digital designer and&amp;nbsp;illustrator. on Laura Sinclair</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CareerFoundry</title>
      <link>/experience/careerfoundry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experience/careerfoundry/</guid>
      <description>Execute on all phases of the design process, from wireframing concepts and mockups through to handovers to developers. Improving branding image and consistency through digital materials for social media, presentations, website assets, sales collaterals, etc. Identifying and understanding customer needs, and work with team members to improve their online experience. Translating ideas and concepts into compelling, visual solutions. Working in close collaboration with lots of different teams, including designers, developers, marketing strategists, copywriters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustrations</title>
      <link>/work/illustration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/illustration/</guid>
      <description>                                         This is something I wonder about very often.
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CareerFoundry</title>
      <link>/work/careerfoundry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/careerfoundry/</guid>
      <description>My missions include:   Execute on all phases of the design process, from wireframing concepts and mockups through to handovers to developers.
 Improving branding image and consistency through digital materials for social media, presentations, website assets, sales collaterals, etc.
 Identifying and understanding customer needs, and work with team members to improve their online experience.
  Translating ideas and concepts into compelling, visual solutions.
 Working in close collaboration with lots of different teams, including designers, developers, marketing strategists, copywriters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixiyo</title>
      <link>/experience/pixiyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experience/pixiyo/</guid>
      <description>Handling projects from intake to production, then delivery - making sure they were shipped right on time. And that our clients had a smile on their face 🙂 Designing, coding and maintaining websites, using Wordpress (we all know how this goes 🤯) Creating brand identities, defining their guidelines (logos, colours, fonts, etc.) Visual assets for various brands, the usual stuff. Social media banners, icons, etc.  Our biggest project was for Valdys Group, who offers all-inclusive spa, restaurants and hotels resorts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murals</title>
      <link>/work/murals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/murals/</guid>
      <description>         </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vupar</title>
      <link>/experience/vupar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experience/vupar/</guid>
      <description> Design and coding of HTML e-mail campaigns (coding from scratch and testing emails with Litmus, then using MJML ❤️) Working closely with our Creative Director to create and/or update assets for print and digital marketing materials That means: landing pages, social media assets, websites, blogs, corporate identities, business cards, and banner ads. Communicating with our clients about details surrounding their requests, gathering additional information if necessary  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malabar Design</title>
      <link>/experience/malabar-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experience/malabar-design/</guid>
      <description>I was in charge of producing and delivering assets for the brand.
 LOTS of photo editing and retouching Delivering 4000+ graphic assets Adjusting to each brand’s visual guidelines Extremely short deadlines, last-minute requests  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper</title>
      <link>/work/paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/paper/</guid>
      <description>            Behind the scenes&amp;hellip;      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moneo Payment Solutions</title>
      <link>/experience/moneo-payment-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experience/moneo-payment-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Moneo Resto:
 Designing Moneo Resto’s website Designing their whole app, allowing you to check and credit your account, share the bill with friends, report a stolen/lost card Designing business cards, social media assets, and smart cards  Moneo Etudiant:
 Creating assets for online advertising campaigns. Each campaign included: social media assets, website background ads, flyers, html emails, facebook game templates Designing and building a student community blog Creating material, like videos, guides, or mascots, to promote the brand  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting</title>
      <link>/work/painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/painting/</guid>
      <description>             </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoda app</title>
      <link>/work/yoda-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/yoda-app/</guid>
      <description>    And as a bonus, I designed a few placeholder avatar pictures 🙂
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharefood</title>
      <link>/work/sharefood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/sharefood/</guid>
      <description>        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancake ad</title>
      <link>/work/pancake-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/pancake-ad/</guid>
      <description>      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketches</title>
      <link>/work/sketches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/sketches/</guid>
      <description>             </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brittany Ferries</title>
      <link>/work/brittanyferries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/brittanyferries/</guid>
      <description>They were coded from scratch and tested with with Litmus, to make sure they&#39;d work well no matter the email client. Then we moved on to using MJML &amp;#10084;&amp;#65039;
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home page</title>
      <link>/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Advertisement :)
 pica - high quality and fast image resize in browser. babelfish - developer friendly i18n with plurals support and easy syntax.  You will like those projects!
 h1 Heading 8-) h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Horizontal Rules    Typographic replacements Enable typographer option to see result.
(c) (C) (r) (R) (tm) (TM) (p) (P) +-
test.. test&amp;hellip; test&amp;hellip;.. test?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>